まずは いつものメンバー
大胆あいつの攻撃
バイバイ気づいてない振り
大胆あいつの衝撃 まさに生き地獄
荒川河川敷には
いろいろな人たちが住んでいます
そんな人たちにも それぞれに
考えていること 人生があるのです
そしてお話には特に絡んでこないけど
チラチラと画面の端に現れる人たち
目覚めのキッスはまどろむあなたに
あやかしリップなお姫様
寝起きのキックは挨拶代わりに
生足いっつも傷だらけ
ジーザスお向かいさんなの
聞いてやばいの
出会いの切符は夢見るあなたに
まやかしVIPなエア・フォース
時間がないの いま何時？
授業開始の５分前
ということで今日はこの３人に
焦点を絞ってみることにします
ヴィーナスお隣さんなの どうして？
知らない間に
急いでないの いま大事
あなたに出会う５分前
Along the Arakawa riverside...
All kinds of people live here.
手持ちのチップをあの子に賭けたら
まばたきみっつでノック・ダウン
First, there are the regulars.
嫌いじゃないの 嫌なだけ
予測出来ないこの気持ち
期待しないで 暇なだけ
あなたと消える５分間
Then there are the ones who
don't show up too often,
Samurai
but who wander in and out of each scene.
ヴィーナスあの子はいつでもそうなの？
いまなら間に合う
They also have their own lives.
ジーザス引き返せないの 早く気付いて
With that in mind,
we'll be focusing on three such characters today.
Chapter 101: "Last Samurai"
Nino sometimes pays me a
visit while she's sleeping.
ニノさんはたまに寝ぼけて
うちに寝に来るわけだが
And there's one thing I've
been really curious about.
その度に俺は気になっている事がある
Nino...
ニノさん その寝ぐせは
簡単に直るもんなんですか？
How do you deal with your
hair when it's like this?
水圧を利用すれば何とか…
I dunno, I just use the pressure of the deep.
That's one stubborn case of bed head.
かなりガッツのある寝ぐせなわけですね
朝の漁は
ヘアスタイリングも兼ねているからな
I let my morning fishing expedition
handle all my styling needs.
ロングヘアは お手入れ大変でしょうね
Long hair must be a real pain to take care of.
Would it be better if it was shorter?
短いと楽なのか？
Well, maybe.
そりゃあ あっ そうだ
Oh, sure!
If styling it's such a pain,
why not go get a little trim?
もし寝ぐせを直すのが辛いなら
ちょっと短くしたらどうです？
Oh, good idea! Maybe I should just shave it all o—
おおーっ そうだな
どうせだったら全部抜…
ふっ 散髪ダメ！ ぜったーい！
Just say NO to haircuts!
Oh, Hoshi.
おう 星
You freaking stalker!
このストーカー野郎！
入ってくるタイミングがよすぎだろう！
Don't tell me you being here is just a coincidence!
ニノがケダモノの家に
入ってゆくのが見えたからな
I just happened to see Nino
stumble into some beast's den.
人知れず見守るのもナイトの仕事
It's a knight's duty to protect
his princess from the darkness!
じゃあ 俺もトリートメントに行こうかな
Maybe I should go have my hair treated, too.
My cuticles have been freaking
out from all the stress lately...
最近ストレスでキューティクルが
失われつつあるんだよねぇ
Where'd you sprout up from?!
あんたもどっから湧いたー！
じゃあ みんなも誘って美容院に行くか
Let's get everyone together
and head to the salon.
Oh yeah!
おうよっ
Nino! Don't get it cut, okay? Seriously!
ニノ… 切らないでくれよ 本当に
Jeez... why does a costumed freak
need a haircut, anyway?
まったく… 着ぐるみ野郎に散髪も何も
You too, Rec.
リク お前もだぞ
Yeah, your hair's getting pretty shaggy.
ああ かなり髪伸びてるしな
Yup. It's like twice as long as before.
うん うざさ倍増してるもん
いやですよ
俺 専属のカリスマ美容師ついてますから
No thank you.
I already have my own private hair stylist.
We're all going.
みんなで行こう
Not me.
行きませんよ
Come on.
一緒に行くんだ
嫌ですって！
I said no!
だって美容院って…
美容院って言ったら あの人が…！
You call it a salon,
but that salon—
—he's lurking!
We're here!
たのもー！
Samurai
Welcome!
いらっしゃーい
Samurai
Yo, Last Samurai!
よう ラストサムライ
ニノはトリートメントだけだから
Nino's just here for a shampoo treatment!
See? I told you.
ほら 出ちゃったじゃん
And after I spent the last 12 episodes
trying to avoid him!
せっかく「12 BRIDGE」まで
フラグ立てないようにしてたのにー！
Chapter 102: "Haircut"
今日は大勢で来たぜーい
The whole gang's here today.
Make me super cute, 'kay?
今日もかわいくお願いね
いすは パイプいすになるが
いいでござるか？
Do you mind sitting on these folding chairs?
うっう…
視界の隅にチラチラ入ってはいたが
He's been moving through my peripheral.
But I've been desperately avoiding
an actual encounter.
今まで必死に決定的な出会いを
避けていたのに…
No... I won't give up yet!
いや しかし俺はまだ諦めないぞ
あくまで客と美容師として接すれば…
I just happen to be a customer,
and he just happens to be the stylist.
うん 拙者 君の事は
ずっと気になっていたでござる
By the by...
I've had my eye on you for quite some time.
That luscious head of black
hair is almost too perfect.
地毛とは思えぬほど見事な黒髪
もしかして毛先にブルーを入れて…
Do you happen to use blue dye?
いや サムライブルー入れてる？
No, perhaps you use Samurai Blue?
いえ 何も
Nope. Sure don't.
Look at that! He's determined to sneak
in samurai jokes whenever he can!
ほら やっぱり言い直してまで
サムライネタ入れてきたー！
Last Samurai, I need a little trim, too.
ラストサムライ
俺もカットだけしたいんだけど
Could you color the tips like baby corn?
私は毛先をヤングコーンっぽくして
前髪はプチトマトな感じ
And make my bangs like cherry tomatoes?
But the overall feel should be like
a cucumber, just like normal.
もちろん全体の印象はキュウリよりにね
ござる
Verily.
Thank goodness. He went the other way.
よかった
あっち行ってくれた
Rec, this isn't the first time you've
been around Last Samurai, right?
リク お前 ラストサムライに会うの
初めてじゃねえだろう
Yeah. So why are you acting so shy around him?
それなのに ずいぶん他人行儀だね
あっ 当たり前ですよ
だって ちょんまげの美容師って
I can't help it!
He's a barber with a topknot.
He might give me a topknot
if he catches me off-guard.
隙見せたら
俺までちょんまげにされそうだし
はははは 何だお前
Oh, grow up!
なあ ラストサムライ こいつ お前に
まげ結われそうでこえーんだって
Ya hear that, Last Samurai? He's scared
you're gonna give him a topknot.
Hey! Sh—
え？ あはは そんなのしないでござるよ
Huh?
Perish the thought!
On you, a topknot would look simply atro—
だって君 ちょんまげ似合いそうもない…
ああ うう…
あ ああ いやっ 違うよー おっ
そういうアレじゃなくて…
N-No, I just mean—
It wouldn't be that bad. Indeed,
you might look quite fetching!
ふんっ 似合うと思うし…
Shall we try it?
言おうか？
えーっ！ おおっ
なに俺 気遣わせちゃった？
What? Why are you acting so weird?!
I just mean—it's not like you would look horrible.
ううん 絶対に似合わないってわけじゃ…
ちょっとシャギー入れたら ううん
If I just layered it here...
Yes!
At least he's not too forceful or anything.
でも ちょんまげを
強制してくる人じゃなかったのか
思ったより普通の人なんだな
He might turn out to be kind of normal.
Were you really that nervous, Sir Rec?
もしかしてリク殿は
緊張していたでござるか？
え？ ああ まあ… すみません
Well... yeah, sorry.
Would you like a sample from
my impression repertoire?
じゃあ モノマネでも見る？
あはっ モノマネですか？
Impression repertoire?
ふふん いくよっ 坂本竜馬 んっ
Ready? This is Sakamoto Ryoma.
My shoulder huuuurts!
肩こるーっ
よおー
Well?
どう？
That was an everyday Ryoma!
竜馬の日常 切り取ってきたー！
うはははは
ちょっと世代が違うんじゃない？
He might be too young for that one.
We get it, but it's a bit dated.
俺たちは分かるけどよ 古いよー
ああー
ジェネレーションギャップでござったか
Ahh, is this what you call a "generation gap"?
さて そろそろ仕事に
取りかかるでござる
Well...
'Tis time to get to work, methinks.
I've got a full schedule today.
今日は人数も多いし
シスター殿もいるでござるからな
And Sister's here, as well.
すまんな
Sorry.
What's the big deal about Sister being here?
シスターがいると何か不都合が…？
よしっ これで後はシスター殿でござるか
Excellent. Now the only one left is Sister.
Cool. Rec, we should get going.
さっ リク もう出たほうがいいぜ
Yeah, hurry up.
そうよ 早く
Wait! How did he—
いやっ ていうかどうやって？
さあて じゃあシスター殿 今日はどう…
So then, Sister... what kind of cut would you—
隙ありー！！
YOU'RE MINE!
くうっ くっ
すまん… また避けてしまった
つい反射的に申し訳ない
Sorry.
I dodged again. It's just a natural
reflex. I'm really sorry.
は はははは シスター殿
動くとかえって危ないでござるよ
Sister, this is much more dangerous
if you can't stop dodging.
そんなの… 見えてたら そりゃ避けるよ！
That...
Anyone would try to dodge that!
Chapter 103: "Billy and Jacqueline"
いいやー！
Not yet!
なんのー！ せいやー！
Is it too much to hope for one single
normal person down here?
やっぱりこの橋の下に
まともな人間なんていないのか…
あ あの二人たしか
ビリーとジャクリーンっていう…
Oh. That's...
Billy and Jacqueline, I think.
"I love you." Say, " I love you."
愛してる 愛してるよ
Is she teaching him how to talk? So he's a parrot?
言葉を教えてるのか？
やっぱりオウムなんだなぁ
That's the premise.
設定は
Anyway, he must be the easiest to get along
with. He probably doesn't talk much.
まあ余計なことしゃべらないだけ
一番かわいいかも
Come on, Billy. "I love you."
ねえビリー 愛してる
ぺっ おい 黙れよ
Yo. Shut it.
他人の言葉を借りる人生なんて
俺はもう卒業したんだよ
Spitting back other peoples' words—
That part of my life is over.
ぺっ ビリーのビリーは
ロカビリーのビリーだ
Billy's "Billy" comes from rockabilly's "billy."
だって… だって私 不安なんだもん
But... But I... I just have to hear you say it!
Quit your squawkin'! Damn!
泣くんじゃねえ！ うざってえ
だって私たちみたいな不倫の関係…！
But... our forbidden love!
Forbidden
Love
ふ 不倫っ！ なんだ？
この橋の下にあるまじきディープな話は？
Forbidden?! That's way too deep and
inappropriate to be discussed down here!
I'm just scared...
不安よ
If my 30,000 children and 10,000 husbands
back at home find out about this—
もしもこのことが巣にいる三万匹の子供と
一万匹の旦那に知られたらって思うと…
Ahh.
And you never tell me how you feel about me!
あなたは全然気持ちを言ってくれないし
ねえ オウム返しでもいいから言ってほしいのよ
Listen. I don't care if you just repeat what I say.
Please, tell me, "I love you, Jacqueline!"
愛してる ジャクリーンって
Lying just ain't my thing.
嘘はつかない主義だ
And I'd be lying if I repeated you.
お前のオウム返しじゃ
嘘になっちまうからな
Jeez! I know this is none of my business...
But that's really harsh!
それって俺が口をはさむことじゃないけど
ちょっと冷たすぎるんじゃ？
"I love you"?
愛してる？ へっ 笑わせるな
Hah! Don't make me laugh.
Such a stereotypical string of words can't convey
even a hundredth of my true feelings.
そんな使い古された言葉じゃ
俺の気持ちの100分の１も表せやしない
The 10,000 drones back at your hive
巣にいる一万の男が束になっても
俺の思いには かないやしねえんだぜ
don't mean squat next to the
feelings I have for you.
うっ いっ ビリー！
Billyyyy!
-はあ…
-うるせいっ！
Cram it!
Now that's true love.
愛でござるな
A beautiful sight.
美しいな
I'll do whatever it takes to
stay far away from them.
何にしても関わりたくないと思いました
Chapter 104: "Arakawa Dreamland"
きはは
ひいい
The fair was so much fun!
楽しかったね 遊園地
Good. We'll go back again sometime.
ああ また連れてってやるからな
やったー！
Yay!
Kids, please pay attention during cla—
おい お前ら授業中によそ見するんじゃ
A fair... that sounds awesome.
いいなー 遊園地
行ってみたいなー
I wanna go, too.
That's right.
そうか 鉄人兄弟は昔 研究所で
今は河川敷だもんな
The twins were trapped at the lab,
and then came here right afterward.
Man...
まったく 遊園地なんかに
気を取られてないで しっかり勉強しろ！
Stop daydreaming about fairs and start studying!
C'mon, but—
でもだって…
それくらい
明日にでも連れてってやるから
I'll take you to the fair tomorrow.
リクさん…
Rec!
We'll consider it a field trip.
まあ遠足だ 遠足
そんなあ…
Is...
Is that how you're gonna take us back to the
"dreamland" that's really a research lab?!
そうやって僕らを夢の国という名の
研究所に連れて行くつもりだね
出るもんか
絶対に河川敷から出るもんか！
We're not leaving.
We're not leaving Arakawa! No way!
Well then what do you want?!
どっちだ お前らー！
I wanna go to the fair.
行きたいけん 遊園地
でもここからは死んでも出るもんかー！
But we're not leaving! You'll hafta kill us first!
ああー 分かった 分かった
じゃあ遊園地をここに作ってやる
Okay, okay! Then let's have a fair
down here. How's that sound?
それでいいだろ？
ほんとう？
Really?
そんなことできるの？
Can we really do that?
There's nothing I can't do!
俺に不可能などない！
Give me one week, and I'll plan
the best fair you've ever seen.
１週間くらい待ってろ
すごいの作ってやるからな
はーい！
Okay!
Okay. First I'll ask Takai to start planning it.
よし まずは企画を高井に頼んで
Master Ko, all dooone!
行様 できましたぞー！
Mysterious Beauty Master Ko's Land
夢の国がー
It's my dreamland!
Sound of Romance
Master Ko's Sweet Whisper Room
愛してるよ 愛してるよ
I love you. I love you.
Ba-BUMP !
Master Ko's
Lap Freefall
Nope. No way.
は ダメだな
何ができあがるか目に見えるようだ
I can just imagine what he'd do with it.
はあ まあいい
だったらこの俺自ら腕をふるうまでだ
Well then, I'll just have to do it myself.
えーっと 遊園地ってどんなだっけ？
So... what are fairs like?
Fairs... fairs...
遊園地 遊園地…
I've never been to a fair before!
俺も遊園地行ったことねえ！
そりゃあそうだぁ
Of course not. Father was never the kind of
person to take someone out to have fun.
遊びになんて連れてってくれる
父さんじゃなかったもんなあ
わーい わーい
Yay! Yay!
It's gonna be great!
楽しみだー
さすがリクさん
We believe in you, Rec!
よっ えっ まあこの俺なら
行ったことなくたって…
Even if I've never been to one,
my strength and determination can
make any dreamland a reality!
気合いと才能で何とかならないことは！
そして３日後…
And so, three days later...
Hey, Rec!
おーい リクー
何ですか？ すいませんが
今取り込み中なんでまた…
What is it? Sorry, but I'm a little busy right now.
プレゼントだ
Present for ya.
Fun
Rollercoaster
3D Theater
Carousel
え？ これまさか…
And this is...
聞いたぞ 遊園地のこと
I heard about the fair.
Not bad, Rec.
やるじゃない リク
そんなとこに気付いてあげられるなんて
You figured out something every kid needs.
We all put together a fair.
遊園地はみんなで作った
もうオープンしてるから
ステラちゃんたちを連れてきてちょうだい
It's already open, so you can take the kids.
Hey, wai—
ああっ ちょっと
先生の仕事は生徒たちの引率なんだろ？
Teachers are supposed to guide
their students, right?
えっ えへっ ははっ
C'mon, hurry! Hurry!
ほら 早く早くー！
正直助かった
What a relief.
The people down here are pretty
decent folks, after all.
荒川の住人ってなんだかんだ言って
いいやつらなんだよなー
Wow—they did all this in three days? Amazing!
おお ３日でこれってすごいじゃん
よう おせーじゃねえか
夢の国が待ちくたびれてるぜー！
Yo, took ya long enough! The dreamland
was getting tired of waiting for you.
Now... Kappaland's number one
mascot cutie welcomes you!
さあ かぱちゃんランドの
ナンバー１マスコットガールのお出迎えだー！
Huh? They even have a mascot?
へえ マスコットまでいるのか
あっ あそこじゃ！
There she is!
意外とちゃんとして…
This is pretty legitimate.
はっ ようこそだリス
Welcome, friends.
ふ… 今日は心の頬袋を
尻子玉でいっぱいにして帰るリスよ
I'm gonna stuff my cheeks with your
shirikodama and carry them home with me.
な なぜ無理にもう１枚着たんだー！
Why'd you have to squeeze into another suit?!
Hey, not in front of the kids!
There certainly isn't a spirit in here.
やめるリスよ
子供たちの前で
中の妖怪なんていないリスよ
背中のこぶには夢とクルミと尻子玉が
詰まっているリスよー
In here, there are only dreams, walnuts,
and a few shirikodama!
Chapter 105: "Attractions"
Kids.
２人とも あいつボコっていいぞ
You have my permission to beat him!
That's the proper response to
seeing a man in a furry suit!
それが着ぐるみと男子の正しい関係だ
そうなのリクさん？
Are you sure, Rec?
Cool!
じゃあ…
まったく…入口からして既に不安に
And this is only the entrance...
Look, Rec!
見ろ リク！
Whoa, now that's an admirable creation.
あれ？ 案外立派なものが
It's so awesome!
すごいのー
いらっしゃい ステラちゃん 乗る？
Welcome, Stella. Would you like to take a ride?
Yeah!
はっ 僕たちも！
Us, too!
リクくんは
そこの白馬なんてどうかしら？
As for you, Rec...
Why don't you take that white horse there?
えっ 俺がメリーゴーランドですか？
Me? On a carousel?
あはっ なんか恥ずかしいですけど…
じゃあ ちょっとだけ
It's kind of embarrassing, but...
One quick ride can't hurt!
ふあっ しかし すごいですね
このバリエーション
This is really incredible.
Look at all these animals.
They're really well crafted.
They're almost... too real.
その上 作りも豪華っていうか
リアルっていうか
And look at the detailed—
細部までよく作って…
Now... away!
さあ走りなさーい！
ウヒヒィィーン
リアル家畜だー！
THEY'RE ALL REEEAAL!!!
We had a little issue with our budget, ya know?
予算の問題で仕方なく ねっ
And that look on your face—
最高に楽しそうな笑顔で
よく言いますよー！
What the hell was I thinking?!
うっ あっ…
俺は一体何を油断してたんだ
This place is an unamusement park
created by the beasts of Arakawa!
ここは荒川住人が作った
遊園地だってーのに
Revenge of
the Kappa
３Ｄシアター？
A 3D theater?
Revenge of
the Kappa
あはは…
ありがとう
気をつけろ子供たち 一瞬の隙も！
Okay, and here are your 3D glasses.
はい リクくんの分の３Ｄメガネ
えっ ああ はい…
Uh... thanks.
３Ｄシアターか
これなら危険はなさそうだけど…
A 3D theater, huh? We should be safe in here.
おおっ キャスト ニノさんたちかよ
They're the cast members?
Wow! It looks like it's coming
right out of the screen!
すごい！ 本当に飛び出して見える
I'm not sure about the content,
but it definitely feels real.
内容はモロパクリだけど
そこにあるかのような臨場感
And these dramatic sound effects...
圧倒的な音響
How'd they manage to pull
off a full-scale 3D movie?
まさかここまで
本格的な３Ｄシアターを…
わー 弾が飛び出して見えるー
Whoa! The bullets are shooting right at us!
すごいね すごいね
This is so cool!
シスターの銃が超立体的じゃのー
Sister's gun looks super-dimensional!
Hey, you there.
おい観客 立っていると危ないぞ
No standing.
So this is real, too?!
これもリアルか！
３Ｄシアターは
リアルさが売りなのだろ？
A 3D movie is supposed to
be as real as it gets, right?
How about you work on creating
a "dream" land first?!
その前に夢を売ってくださいよ
遊園地を何だと思ってるんですか？
What the heck do you think a fair is?
いやーだってよう 俺らがガキの頃には
遊園地なんて無くってよ
Hey, come on.
It's not like we went to a lot
of fairs when we were little.
True.
ああ 俺らの時代の娯楽っつったら
All I had back then was, like, a river near a village,
where my pops took me once in a while.
たまに親父が連れてってくれた
人里近くの川かな
That's when I really got into
collecting shirikodama.
尻子玉集めに夢中になったぜ
ああ いいですね
Ahh, sounds nice.
My commanding officer would often
take me to the front lines.
私はたまに分隊長につれていってもらえる
最前線が…
Who would want to admire a sunset
in such a bloody place?
そんな血塗られた３丁目で
夕日は見たくないです
Whaaa?
ええー じゃないです！
"Whaaa?" nothing! I refuse to let the kids
play in a dangerous death trap like this!
とにかく こんな不具合だらけな遊園地で
子供たちを遊ばせておくわけにはいきません！
We're leaving.
帰るぞ！
ふええー やだやだやだー
No, no, no!
We wanna keep playing!
まだ遊ぶんじゃい！
おいリク まだ絶叫マシンのチケットが
残ってるじゃないか
Hey, Rec. You still got tickets
for the rollercoaster.
Rollercoaster
どう考えもそれが一番やばそうだろ！
Not true, Rec! It doesn't even go all that fast.
そんなことないよリクくん
そんなに激しく動くようにはしなかったし
シスターくんが相当手間をかけたんだよ
Sister spent a lot of time building it.
I wanna ride it!
乗りたい 乗りたいー！
いいじゃの リク？
Can we, Rec?
今度は大丈夫だ
It'll be fine this time.
Stop being stubborn, Rec. Let 'em ride it!
ケチケチしねえで乗せてやれよ リク
Well... I'm sure it took a lot of work
to build a full-on rollercoaster.
まあ そうりゃあ ジェットコースターなんて
相当大変だったろうしな
Fine. Just this once.
しょうがない いいでしょう
やったー！
Yay!
But make sure you're all buckled in!
そのかわりベルトはしっかり締めろよ！
Okay!
はーい！
But still...
それにしても…
あはっ あれだ！
There it is!
あ あはっ
I can't believe he was able to build a rollercoaster
for the kids in just three days.
この３人のためだけに
３日でジェットコースターを作るなんて
僕が１番だーい
Me first!
Welcome.
はい いらっしゃい
よし ベルトと手錠は
しっかり締めるんだぞ
Make sure the belt and handcuffs
are securely fastened.
ま 相当の痛みは伴うが…
絶叫は間違いなしだ
Now, you might feel a little prick.
Be sure to scream your lungs out.
He's been scared speechless!
声も出なくなってんだろうが！
This is the Iron Maiden Coaster.
アイアンメーデーコースターです
Chapter 106: "The Amazing Parade"
ん… 結局 誰も遊園地のこと
分かってなかったんじゃないか
All in all,
none of them seem to grasp the idea of a fair.
あっ ふっ あはは…
I'm surprised they're having so much fun.
いいのかよ あんなんで
I guess they can turn anyplace
into an amusement park.
まったく… あいつらにかかったら
どこでも遊園地だな
あは はは ははっ…
Rec.
リク
リクさん見て これもらったの！
Look, Rec! Look what I got!
わしゃ赤じゃ
I got a red one!
僕は青
Mine's blue!
そりゃあ よかったな 楽しいか？
That's great, kids. Did you have fun?
Hm? What's this feeling?
あ あれ？ なんかこの感じ…
Yup!
We had—
すっごく！
楽しかった！
—so much fun!
Good. I'm glad.
そうか よかった
Drink this.
飲みなさい
なんだ…
That was...
What's up, Rec?
どうした リク？
今思い出したんです
父さんと遊んだ日のこと
I just remembered something...
A day I spent with my father.
あへっ どうして忘れていたんだろう
あんな珍しいこと
I don't know how I forgot.
It was such a rare event.
聞かせてくれ その思い出のこと
Why don't you tell me about it?
Oh... well...
ああ えっと…
デパートの屋上だったけど父さんが一度だけ…
一度だけ連れて行ってくれたんです
It was just a place on the roof of a department
store. But Father took me there once.
I rode the carousel, and I sat on a bench
with him and drank some juice, and...
メリーゴーランドに乗って
２人でベンチに座ってジュース飲んで
Ah. That sounds...
そうか…
それは うれしいな
really nice.
Yeah.
はい
Let's make more nice memories.
もっと思い出を作ろう
私と みんなと一緒に
Together—you and me and everyone else.
おーい パレードが始まるそうじゃ
Hey! The parade's about to start!
リクさん 早く行こうよ
Rec, c'mon! Let's go!
Ah, sure!
ああ… おう！
はあ パレード！
I wonder if they'll remember this
day later on in their lives.
あいつらも今日のことを
いつか思い出すんだろうか
And me, too.
俺もいつかまた今日のこの日のこと
ニノさんとみんなと過ごした今日のことを
The memory of today...
My memory of the day I spent
with Nino and everyone else.
あっ まぶしいね
セルフライトアップって
Man, this self-lighting thing is blinding me!
We didn't have much of a choice.
The girls used up all the light bulbs.
しょうがねーだろ 女子たちので
豆電球切れちまったんだから
That image
思い出すどころか
脳裏に焼き付いて離れんわー！
will be forever burnt into our memories!
Chapter 107: "Hidden Treasure"
Okay!
The hidden treasure is still safe.
あの日夕暮れ
And there's no sign of intruders.
Chapter 108
愛のカケラ 探すたびに
Drowning in murky waters.
Floating in a small stream.
The emotions we shed.
いつも何故か 寂しくなる
Those unfulfilled days.
As they drift along, their sharp
corners are worn away.
もう行かなくちゃ
Their rounded edges become
like pieces of a puzzle.
この空泣き出す前に
These beautiful pieces.
Perhaps
サカサマになって
you
and you.
君の事探して
いつまでも僕らは
These are the pieces that connect us.
たどり着けないまま
Illustration: Hikaru Nakamura
橋の下に立って
流れる渦に在って
いつまでも僕らは
その答え探して
オーケー 今日モ秘宝ノ無事ヲ確認
侵入サレタ痕跡モナイネ
濁流の中で溺れる
せせらぎの中でたゆたう
はがれ落ちた感情は
何かが足りなかった日常は
流れるうちに角が削れて丸くなり
まるでパズルのピースのような
小さい一欠片に変わる
この愛しい欠片は
この美しい欠片は
きっと
お前と
あなたと
繋がるための一欠片